[
  {
    "question": "Decrease of Utilities Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Membantu perusahaan dalam mengungkap kecurangan yang terjadi, sehingga diberikan promosi. Mendapat reward maju 18 langkah"
  },
  {
    "question": "Increase of Travelling Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Decrease of of Delivery Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Decrease of Advertising Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Increase of Retained Earnings",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Decrease of Depreciation Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Increase of Supplies Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Increase of Maintenance Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Decrease of Training Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  }
]
